zopim.io 2015-06-16

# Zopim Privacy Policy | Zopim

> **Updated May 1, 2014.**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to all products and services offered by Zopim Technologies Pte Ltd (“Zopim,” “we,” or “us”). If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or email us at [support@zopim.com](mailto:IL%7C%1CLM%C2%BCl%0FL%C3%AD%C2%BCM%C3%9D%C2%99%C2%AD%7D%C2%BD). Capitalized terms used but not defined in this Policy shall have the meaning assigned to such terms in Zopim’s Terms of Service (“Terms,” available at www.zopim.com/termsofservice), and Your access to and use of our Service is subject to the Terms. 

#### Information we collect and how we use it

Information you provide

We collect personally identifiable information (“personal information”) from you when you interact with us through our Service. For example, if you register for an account with us, we may ask you for personal information such as email, name, contact details, account password, instant messaging ID and/or credit or payment card information. We also collect personal information such as an email address and a name or alias of any Agents you authorize to use the Service in connection with your account and a password from these Agents when they first access the Service. Credit or payment card data is used to process payments for Subscriptions to the Service. 

By voluntarily providing us with personal information, you hereby represent that you are the owner of such personal information or are otherwise authorized to provide it to Zopim. You further agree that you are consenting to our collection, use, storage and/or disclosure of such personal information in accordance with this Policy. You acknowledge and agree that your communications with Zopim will inevitably result in the transfer of information, including personal information, across international boundaries. If you provide personal information to Zopim through our Service, you acknowledge and agree that such personal information may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Zopim and the authorized third parties referred to herein, located in Singapore, the United States, Canada, Germany, the Netherlands and other countries (the “Other Countries”) for storage and processing in accordance with this Policy. You acknowledge and agree that the privacy and data security laws of such Other Countries may be different from the privacy and data security laws in force in the country in which you reside and agree that the privacy and security laws in effect in the applicable Other Countries may govern how your personal information may be collected, used, stored and/or disclosed. 

Zopim uses "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our Service and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. 

Zopim uses cookies to store your and your Agents preferences and other information on your and their computers in order to save time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display personalized content and appropriate advertising within the Service and on subsequent visits to our websites. We store your unique ID number, and the time you signed in, by placing an encrypted cookie on your hard drive. This cookie allows you to move from page to page within the Service without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. We also use cookies to improve your experience with the Service. For example, your e-mail address may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your e-mail address to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. 

Our live chat widget sets the following cookies: 

  1. **__zlcid** to store the Zopim Live Chat ID used to identify a device across visits, and also across a single chat session, and
  2. **__zprivacy** to store the user's preference to disable Live Chat, and cease using cookies. The __zprivacy cookie is stored across visits.

Our websites enable the use of the Adobe, Inc.’s Flash Player product when you use Our Classic Dashboard. By default, use of the Adobe Flash Player generates “flash cookies” (also known as “persistent identification elements” or “local shared objects”). You can disable, delete and control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Flash Player, located via the following link: http://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html. If you disable, you may not be able to take advantage of certain features on our Classic Dashboard. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. To learn more how to control cookie settings through your browser: 

  * Click [here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) to learn more about the “Private Browsing” setting and cookie setting in FireFox;
  * Click [here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) to learn more about “Incognito” and cookie setting in Chrome;
  * Click [here](http://support.microsoft.com/kb/196955) to learn more about “InPrivate” and cookie setting in Internet Explorer; or 
  * Click [here](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5000?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US) to learn more about “Private Browsing” and cookie setting in Safari. 

If you want to learn more about cookies, or how to control or delete them, please visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance. In addition, certain third party advertising networks, including Google, permit users to opt out of or customize preferences associated with your internet browsing. To learn more about this feature from Google, click [here](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjXTtGfXQdQk5AcU7L85tIzVSqvch_gmK_m5U07Bmx2UsZJEJQkW-d0b8jTKGLhDUUeCrIWASxSkiM1qfHdsShzcuNJCnbOzu1WqA89NKTk9ep07Gj8S2CXPkcjpfSUgTfvZGBshLICLUbp8J4auUvXXKD7eTt-VhbFrYUNgvM_Tp0K0bYLTIpLpICQOHkcCmOIeY93s0W5yuZ1XxESwVyaBrm28A). 

Please note that if you do elect to disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you may not be able to access or take advantage of many features of the Service. 

Many jurisdictions require or recommend that website operators inform users as to the nature of cookies they utilize and, in certain circumstances, obtain the consent of their users to the placement of certain cookies. If you are a customer of Zopim, it is your responsibility to inform the individuals with whom you interact using the Service as to the types of cookies utilized in the Service and, as necessary, to obtain their consent. If you require more specific information as to the nature of the cookies utilized in the Service for purposes of fulfilling these obligations, please contact us by email at [security@zopim.com](mailto:%089Y8X\)%C2%98H%C2%9B%08%C2%A9%C3%B8%C2%99%C3%9D%C3%A99%C3%B9). 

Log information

When you use the Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends during your use of the Service. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

User communications

When you send email or other communication to Zopim, we may collect the personal information you provide us and may use it in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

As a Zopim customer you may receive occasional marketing communications regarding our products and services. You can opt out of receiving marketing communications from Zopim please contact us at [support@zopim.com](mailto:%C2%BD%C2%8D%C3%AD%C2%BD%C2%BCM%C2%9D%C3%BE%C2%BD%1CM%C2%BC,h\\%C2%8CL) or follow the unsubscribe instructions included in our marketing communications. 

Non-Identifiable Data

When you interact with Zopim through the Service, we receive and store certain information, which is collected passively using various cookies and similar technologies, and cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. We also engage third party providers to serve a variety of marketing cookies that track and analyze usage, navigational and other statistical information from visitors to Our Site, which does not include personal information but . Zopim and its service providers may store such information itself or such information may be stored in databases owned and maintained by Zopim or its agents or service providers. Our Service may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to Our Site, the number of visitors to each page of Our Site, or the domain names of Our visitors' Internet service providers. 

When you interact with Zopim through the Site, we use third party providers to serve a variety of marketing and operational cookies that enable us to track and analyze usage, navigational and other statistical information from visitors to the Site, and to improve the operation of the Site. This information does not include personal information though we may reassociate this information with personal information we have collected when it is received. Marketing cookies are also used to track the performance of our advertisements and are employed by third party advertising networks that We utilize. These advertising networks follow online activities of visitors to the Site and use this information to inform, optimize and serve tailored advertisements on the Site or on other Websites they visit that we believe would most effectively promote the Service to you. we also use third parties to collect information that assists us in other methods of “remarketing” our Service to visitors to the Site, including customized email communications. 

Aggregated Information

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve our Customers, Zopim often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the personal and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Zopim may share or otherwise publish or distribute this aggregate data. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Zopim may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe Our Service to current and prospective business partners, customers and to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 

Do Not Track Signals

We do not currently respond to web browsers’ “Do Not Track” signals that provide a method to opt out of the collection information about visitors’ activities on the Site and Service, and across other websites. If we do so in the future, we will provide all relevant information in this Policy. 

#### Information Sharing

Zopim currently processes personal information on its servers located in Singapore, Germany, Canada, the Netherlands and the United States of America. We may change the locations in which we process personal information from time to time, including by commencing personal information processing in additional or different Other Countries. 

Zopim only shares personal information with other third parties outside of Zopim in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We have obtained our customer’s consent.
  * We sometimes hire third parties perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include maintaining databases and processing payments or otherwise providing us with necessary software, networking, storage and other services we use to provide and operate the service. When we employ a third party to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to: 
    1. satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
    2. enforce the Terms, including investigation of potential violations thereof;
    3. detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or;
    4. protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Zopim, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Zopim becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. 

#### Data Integrity

Zopim processes personal information only in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our products and services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. Customers of Zopim may update or change the personal information they have provided to Zopim by logging into the Service and providing such information where applicable. Zopim will retain personal information we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide the Service to our customers. We may further retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, maintain accurate accounting, financial and other operational records and enforce our agreements. Zopim has not direct relationship with the individuals with whom our customers may interact using the Service. Any such individual seeking access to, or who would like to correct, amend or delete data that may be stored in the Service should direct his or her inquiry to the applicable Zopim customer. 

#### Security

Zopim takes reasonable steps to protect personal information collected through our service from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or electronic transmission (including email) is ever fully secure or error free. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via the Internet. 

#### Changes To This Policy

Please note that this Policy may be revised from time to time. We will post any Policy revisions on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice, usually via email. When we post changes to this Policy, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of this statement. We therefore encourage you to periodically review this page for updates to this Policy. Your continued use of the Service after any changes or revisions to this Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Policy. 

#### Other Important Matters

Children

Zopim does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information through our services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Policy by instructing their children never to provide personal information on our Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to Zopim through our Service, please contact us, and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information from our databases. 

Other Products/Services

This Policy only applies to the products and services of Zopim Technologies Ltd and not to the products or services of any other entity, affiliate or other third parties (“Third Parties”), even if such products or services are linked, integrated or sold in conjunction with our Service. Any links, integrations, or co-sales from or with our Service do not imply that Zopim endorses or has reviewed the practices of any such Third Parties. You should contact such Third Parties directly for information on their privacy policies.
